skyscape.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy

Physicians Interactive Holdings (PIH), its affiliates and subsidiaries, including MedManage Systems Inc. and Skyscape, Inc. (collectively, the "Company", "we", "us" and "our") values your confidence in us and respects your privacy. We hold our users and your privacy concerns in the highest regard. This Privacy Policy Statement describes to you our practices regarding the personal information which you give to us, or we obtain about you, from our websites, including but not limited to www.physiciansinteractive.com, www.pichoice.com, www.physinteractive.com, www.samplecenter.com, and www.skyscape.com (collectively, our "websites"), products and services or from our third party partners.

## CONSENT

By using our websites, products or services, you expressly consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy Statement and agree that you are entering into a voluntary business relationship with us for the purpose of conforming with any applicable federal, state and local laws relating to solicitations, including via email, telephone or fax. 

**Children's Information**  
We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from any person under the age of thirteen. No parts of our websites, products or services are designed to attract anyone under the age of thirteen.

**Users Outside Of The United States.**  
Your personal information may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT

One of our primary goals in collecting personal information from you is to give you a meaningful, enjoyable and customized experience while using our websites, products and services and to allow us to develop new products and services that are relevant to visitors like you. Personal information also allows us to provide specific services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize the webpage or service to make your online experience smooth and efficient.

## What We Collect

**Personal Information**  
We collect the following types of information from you when you register for an account on our website: name, shipping address, phone number, fax number, email address, date of birth, and demographics. For the use or purchase of certain products or services, we also collect professional designation, specialty, state license number, medical school and year of graduation and (during a purchase) credit card information and billing address. If you voluntarily provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply. When you voluntarily participate in one of our surveys or programs (as described in further detail below), we may collect additional user information.

**Non-Personal Information**  
In addition to gathering information through the registration of users, may also monitor the use of our website, services and/or products by collecting aggregate, anonymous, non-personal information. Typically, this information tracks users patterns throughout the PIH's websites, and it may include information such as your browser type, operating system, date/time stamp for your visit, IP address, domain name, referring URLs, statistics about the number of visitors to the site, the number of pages visited, and user response rates. This information enables us to provide a more enjoyable and personalized experience, as well as tracking errors.

**Cookies**  
Additionally, when you use our products, services or websites, we may monitor your use of the website by collecting aggregate information through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small pieces of information that a website transfers to the memory or hard drive on your computer. For instance, when you visit one of our websites, our web server will automatically recognize some non-personal information, including but not limited to the date and time you visited our site, the pages you visited, the referrer (the website you came from), the type of browser you are using (e.g. Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), and the domain name and address of your Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Verizon, AOL).

Most web browsers have options that allow you to control whether or not to accept cookies. However, disabling cookies in your browser may prevent access to some parts of PIH's website, services, or products.

**Market Research Information**  
Users of PIH's websites, products and/or services may also elect to participate in market research surveys or programs. By submitting answers to these surveys or programs, you are providing specific feedback to us and/or certain third parties (as described below). Participation in a survey or program is voluntary and you have the opportunity to decline participation or honoraria. If you elect to participate in a survey or program, we may disclose your information to certain third parties (as described below), provided you have given us a consent to do so.

**Information Collected from Other Sources**  
We may occasionally supplement your information with information we receive from other sources including, but not limited to (a) companies that provide our products or services by way of a co-branded or private-labeled website, (b) companies (e.g., pharmaceutical companies) that sponsor surveys or programs on our website (the entities in (a) and (b), collectively, "Partner Companies"), (c) downloadable software applications from our websites or (d) professional organizations such as the American Medical Associations, which we will add to the information which we already hold about you.

## How Information is Used

We use the information we collect to administer our business activities, improve our website, products and services, provide customer service, make available products and services to our users and customers, and for the recruiting, marketing, and other business purposes of PIH and our Partner Companies.

Without limiting the foregoing, this information helps us to create your account, verify your identity, verify your eligibility for products and services, deliver interactive educational programs, provide you support, initiate and fulfill orders, complete transactions, and administer the website.

Without limiting the foregoing, we may use your personal information to communicate with you. For example, we may correspond with you, possibly through email, direct mail, fax, or phone calls related to your transactions and orders, participation in our surveys, programs and services, invitations to new surveys or programs and services, deliver information about new surveys, programs or services, and to alert you to developments in the use of pharmaceuticals or selected information from the pharmaceutical industry related to your medical specialty. We use contact and demographic information to offer participation in surveys or programs. We may need to respond to your comments or requests for information; or we may contact you if needed in the course of processing or shipping products or services offered through our websites. We may also use contact and demographic information to extend offers to you from our Partner Companies.

## Disclosing Personal Information

In order to provide you with our website, services, and/or products, we may share your information with our suppliers, agents, contractors, or other service providers ("Service Providers") in connection with the services they perform. Our Service Providers are required not to sell, share, or use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by Company.

We may disclose your personal information to our Partner Companies, who may use this information to provide services requested by PIH and/or for their recruiting, marketing or other business purposes. For example, without limitation, (1) if you have elected to participate in a survey or program, we may share your personal information with the sponsors of the survey or program, when we report the results of the survey or program to the sponsors; and (2) if you accessed our website, product, or service through a co-branded website, we may share your personal information with the co-branded website provider. We do not control the privacy practices of our Partner Companies.

There are specific limited instances when personal information may be shared with accredited Continuing Medical Education ("CME") providers for their fulfillment of their reporting obligations under the Accreditation Council for Continuing Medical Education ("ACCME") and other accrediting bodies. We do not control the privacy practices of these third parties.

We may create aggregate non-personally identifiable information from personal information about our users, sales, products or traffic patterns ("anonymous information"); this anonymous information does not include any personally identifiable information. We use this anonymous information to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our website, products, surveys and/or services. PIH reserves the right to use and disclose anonymous information to third parties in its discretion.

**Disclosure by Law**  
PIH may use or disclose personal information if it believes in good faith that such use or disclosure is necessary to (a) help identify any person attempting to break into or damage our website, (b) to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding any illegal activities, (c) to comply with relevant laws, or legal or regulatory obligations, (d) to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on PIH, or (e) to protect or defend the rights or property of PIH or its customers. Without limiting the foregoing, we may share personal information with law enforcement agencies if we believe that we have evidence of a violation of computer security or related laws.

## PROTECTION OF YOUR DATA

PIH has a number of security measures in place to help protect and safeguard your personal information from accidental loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or accidental destruction.

Although no web site can guarantee the absolute security of your information, we are committed to taking commercially reasonable precautions as described below.

These procedures include the use of firewalls, secure connections on PIH websites, and frequently the use of Secured Socket Layers (SSLs) that encrypt pages that collect sensitive information. Personal information is stored in limited access servers and physical access to our servers requires individual authorization and authentication. Only authorized PIH employees or contractors carrying out permitted functions are allowed access to personal information. In addition, each employee and contractor of PIH is required to sign a confidentiality agreement requiring him or her to keep confidential all personal information of users and customers. We train our employees and contractors on proper use and handling of personal information. Employees and contractors who violate these policies may be subject to disciplinary action, termination of their employment and legal action. Our Service Providers are also required to maintain security measures similar to PIH. However, for added protection, we ask that you keep your login information and passwords confidential.

## UPDATING YOUR DATA

It is important to us that you are able to take an active role in your experience with us. We highly recommend that you confirm and update your profile regularly. You can update or change your profile, which includes personal information, online at any time. You may request deletion of your personal information by us, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. While updating your profile, you can select the type of messages and communications that you want to receive, which will further customize your experience as described below.

## CHOICES

**Promotional Communications.** As described above, we may periodically provide you (via email, mail, phone, or fax) marketing communications promoting the websites, products and services of the PIH, our Partner Companies, and/or other third parties. When you receive marketing communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us by "opting-out" (a) via the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or (b) by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Privacy Policy Statement and other service-related, non-marketing, communications. 

**Your Privacy Rights.** As described above, we may provide your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. You may indicate a preference for us to stop providing your information to third parties for their marketing purposes by "opting-out" by contacting us directly (please see our information below). After you opt-out, we will stop disclosing your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes, unless you have "opted-in" by (a) contacting us directly (please see our information below) or (b) by signing up for another survey and/or program. If you wish to discontinue receipt of marketing e-mails from third parties to whom we've already disclosed your personal information, please contact the third parties directly to update your preferences. 

Questions about our privacy policy or request regarding our privacy policy can be directed to us at [Privacy@PhysiciansInteractive.com](mailto:Privacy@PhysiciansInteractive.com)

Physicians Interactive  
Attn: Customer Service  
950 Technology Way, Suite 202  
Libertyville, Illinois 60048  
Phone: 800.794.6757

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT

This Privacy Policy Statement is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy Statement will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our site. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our website, products or services. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy Statement may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your personal information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of our website, products, or services, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

## OTHER RELEVANT INFORMATION

We may share some or all of your personal information with our affiliates, in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy Statement.

If PIH is (or its assets are) sold, acquired, merged with another entity, or if PIH becomes insolvent, and/or declares bankruptcy (each a "Company Change Event"), the websites, products and services and any information obtained through them, including personal information, may be transferred or sold to another entity in connection with the Company Change Event. That entity will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy Statement.

The headings of sections of this Privacy Policy Statement are for convenience and are not to be used in interpreting this Agreement. As used in this Privacy Policy Statement, the word "including" means "including but not limited to."

PIH websites may contain links to and from other websites, products or services. These other sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy Statement, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other sites. 

Privacy Policy Statement updated on August 25, 2010.  
  
Copyright ©2013 Skyscape.com, Inc. Skyscape® is the registered trademark of Skyscape.com, Inc.  
All other trademarks, service marks and registrations are the intellectual properties of their respective owners.
